<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NoahHaile.com blog, projects &amp; updates</title>
    <link>https://noahhaile.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NoahHaile.com blog, projects &amp; updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:57:26 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://noahhaile.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;motivation&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really have the best of memories and writing has been something I very much enjoy. So it will be an excuse to remember things and keep life a little more interesting! I will use this space to indulge myself and with any luck, people will find value in it. I will put here one of two things:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content that helps you get unstuck:&#xA;These are the answers you desperately need when you know what you want to accomplish, but tools or circumstances become obstacles. Whenever I make it out of such a hole, I will document the processes here so other people wil have an easier time climbing out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What They Don’t Teach You About Learning Online</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/onlinelearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/onlinelearning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The internet has given us access to an infinite library of knowledge, yet navigating it can feel more like wading through quicksand than walking into a well-organized classroom. Learning online seems straightforward&amp;hellip; find a course, watch videos, take notes but nothing is ever so simple. You often times just walk away with frustration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-the-hidden-skill-of-finding-the-right-resources&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. The Hidden Skill of Finding the Right Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s not just about Googling the first thing that pops into your mind. That random YouTube tutorial might seem helpful at first, but twenty minutes in, you realize the creator skimmed over the exact concept you’re struggling with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Artists Steal - Guide to SEO Competitor Analysis</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/greatartistssteal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/greatartistssteal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Less than &lt;strong&gt;3% of consumers&lt;/strong&gt; say they never search for local businesses online. That means nearly everyone—your potential customers included—relies on the internet to find services and products near them. And the trend is only growing stronger. Whether you run a restaurant, coffee shop, or hair salon, the opportunity to tap into this digital traffic is enormous. If your business isn’t online, the hard truth is: you’re falling behind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The good news? It’s never too late to catch up. And the first step is simple—&lt;strong&gt;look at what your competitors are doing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why They Tell You to Work Smart</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/worksmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/worksmart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bob comes home to his wife, Alice, after a long day. He sinks into his favorite recliner, puts his feet up, and listens to the evening news. Meanwhile, Alice prepares supper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can you guess what Bob did all day?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Far more can be inferred from the context of this story than from simply knowing that Bob “worked.” Was he building houses under the scorching sun, or typing feverishly at a keyboard in an air-conditioned office? How much hardship did he endure? What did he truly accomplish?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do I need Local SEO?</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/doineedseo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/doineedseo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A strong online presence is no longer optional&amp;hellip; it’s essential. Today, more than half of all customer acquisition happens online, making your digital presence as important, if not more so, than having a prime physical location. For local businesses, one of the most powerful tools at your disposal is Google’s &lt;strong&gt;Map Pack&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Map Pack is a set of three Google Maps-based results that appear prominently on the first page of search results when users conduct local searches. Essentially, when Google detects that someone is looking for something nearby, the Map Pack shows up front and center. Don’t believe it? Search “[business_type] near me,” and you’ll see it in action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First article&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
