<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on NoahHaile.com blog, projects &amp; updates</title>
    <link>https://noahhaile.com/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on NoahHaile.com blog, projects &amp; updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 10:57:26 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://noahhaile.com/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What They Don’t Teach You About Learning Online</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/onlinelearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/onlinelearning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The internet has given us access to an infinite library of knowledge, yet navigating it can feel more like wading through quicksand than walking into a well-organized classroom. Learning online seems straightforward&amp;hellip; find a course, watch videos, take notes but nothing is ever so simple. You often times just walk away with frustration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-the-hidden-skill-of-finding-the-right-resources&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. The Hidden Skill of Finding the Right Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s not just about Googling the first thing that pops into your mind. That random YouTube tutorial might seem helpful at first, but twenty minutes in, you realize the creator skimmed over the exact concept you’re struggling with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why They Tell You to Work Smart</title>
      <link>https://noahhaile.com/articles/worksmart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noahhaile.com/articles/worksmart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bob comes home to his wife, Alice, after a long day. He sinks into his favorite recliner, puts his feet up, and listens to the evening news. Meanwhile, Alice prepares supper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can you guess what Bob did all day?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Far more can be inferred from the context of this story than from simply knowing that Bob “worked.” Was he building houses under the scorching sun, or typing feverishly at a keyboard in an air-conditioned office? How much hardship did he endure? What did he truly accomplish?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
