<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SEO on NoahHaile.com blog, projects &amp; updates</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SEO on NoahHaile.com blog, projects &amp; updates</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:57:26 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Great Artists Steal - Guide to SEO Competitor Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/greatartistssteal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/greatartistssteal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Less than &lt;strong&gt;3% of consumers&lt;/strong&gt; say they never search for local businesses online. That means nearly everyone relies on the internet to find services and products near them. And the trend is only growing stronger. Whether you run a restaurant, coffee shop, or hair salon, the opportunity to tap into this digital traffic is enormous. If your business isn&amp;rsquo;t online, the hard truth is: you&amp;rsquo;re falling behind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The good news? It&amp;rsquo;s never too late to catch up. And the first step is simple. &lt;strong&gt;Look at what your competitors are doing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do I need Local SEO?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writing/doineedseo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:57:26 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/doineedseo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A strong online presence is no longer optional&amp;hellip; it’s essential. Today, more than half of all customer acquisition happens online, making your digital presence as important, if not more so, than having a prime physical location. For local businesses, one of the most powerful tools at your disposal is Google’s &lt;strong&gt;Map Pack&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Map Pack is a set of three Google Maps-based results that appear prominently on the first page of search results when users conduct local searches. Essentially, when Google detects that someone is looking for something nearby, the Map Pack shows up front and center. Don’t believe it? Search “[business_type] near me,” and you’ll see it in action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
